A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Program Files, Accession 2013:074, SG 2 FA1332
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Program Files, Accession 2013:074, SG 2
1997-2010
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund.
FA1332
5.2 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
This accession contains files from the following Commonwealth Fund programs: Task Force on Academic Health Centers, State Innovation Program (Health Reform), and Child Development and Preventive Care.
Arrangement
Records remain in original order as received.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund archives was donated to Rockefeller Archive Center in 1985. This material was transferred to RAC by the Commonwealth Fund in 2013, as Accession 2013:074.
- Commonwealth Fund records, Program Files, Accession 2013:074, undated; 4.8 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes
  - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Journal Articles, Authors A-F, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Publications: Book Chapters, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Publications and Reports, 40 items (Box 1, Folder 3-7)
  - Committee on the Roles of Academic Health Centers in the 21st Century (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Journal Articles, Authors G-Z (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Meeting materials and reports, 1997-2006 (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
  - Comprehensive Congressional Health Reform Bill of 2009: A Look at Health Insurance, Delivery System and Financing Provisions (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - State Innovation Program Files - Health Reform, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 3-25)
  - Bright Futures Training Intervention: Implementation Curriculum, 2008-2010 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - National Early Intervention, Part C Coordinator Survey and Inventory, 2008-2010 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Child Development and Preventative Care (Ed Schor) - General Files (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Still Images, 2013:074:001; .22 Cubic Feet; 7 sheets of still image slides (Box SF 1)
    - Slide Carousel, 2013:074:002; .22 Cubic Feet (Box SF 1)
    - Behavioral Development in Well-Child Care, 2013:074:003; 45 Digital items
      Conditions Governing Access
      Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Bright Future Systems Toolkit (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bright Futures System Toolkit, 2013:074:004; 1 Digital Item
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Briefing Book (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - 9745: Washington Business Group, Carol Cronin (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Bright Futures Training Intervention: Facilitator's Guide, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - ASQ-3: Ages and Stages Questionnaires (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - ASQ: Ages and Stages Questionnaires, 2013:074:005; 1 Digital Item
  - Healthy Steps Seminar, October 24, 1999; 2013:074:006; 1 Audio Visual item
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further assistance.
  - Healthy Steps for Young Children, Multimedia Package Videos, 2013:074:007; 2 Audio/Visual item
  - Discipline: Teaching Limits with Love, 2013:074:008; 1 Audio/Visual item
  - Comprehensive Care for Children, 2013:074:009; 1 Audio/Visual item
  - Investigate Reports: Every Parents Nightmare, 2013:074:010; 1 Audio/Visual item
  - Begin with Love, Civitas: Tools for Shaping Children's Lives, 2013:074:011; 1 Audio/Visual item
  - "Escape Fire", 2013:074:012; 1 Audio/Visual item
  - Healthy Steps for Young Children: Highlights from Teachable Moments: Infants, 2013:074:013; 2 Audio Visual items
  - I Am Your Child, Ready to Learn, 2013:074:014; 1 Audio/Visual item
  - I Am Your Child, Quality Child Care: Making the Right Choices for You and Your Child, 2013:074:015; 1 Audio/Visual item
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Health Screening for Children and Adolescents: Providers Toolkit (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Recognizing Child Abuse (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Recognizing Child Abuse: A Guide for the Concerned, 2013:074:016; 1 Published Item
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Recognizing Child Abuse: Overhead Transparencies (Box 4, Folder 11)